guys - mix this point to of
records about alignment in this garlic we
look at me and mathematical and optical
sizing so let's get started here
first let's see what is not kill him you might not the
green precious information
under different directions in the real
world 100 in optical illusion is wealth
stash dispersed Vedas and income
present weather rain in various different
from reality show is
n't that political adjustment is
important in graphic design pure number
one region is that creates visually appealing
and balance piece number 283 infosys and
understanding of message and lastly
without optical adjustments readers can be
imported from comprehension slogans fancy which one seems difficult
you will give you moment to observe
and this pass video is
plain mode on which one day to understand iska but
this for most people start with square
is the biggest bird in  watch the video
then subscribe to the page if you liked
the video then subscribe to subscribe
the channel please subscribe and
subscribe this problem subscribe
and stay healthy
120 lines ancient after effect of birth
same size selected in action with and
explain gift you need to understand
what tak line and bases in trophy that you
line this line indicating the height of the
prakash letter when they talk about 20 line
sign in now imaginary and center line upon which
the best of each letter has not been done with
knowledge is let's see how to shoot products
suvvi suvvi is that remove non squash
courts in more parts subscribe and
like this
80's this is look at the pick up the triangle
will spoil the packs this point
is mood pass tak airplane in research chal
vihar to movie pass kya plan and base
line hai
mein vastu tips mostly used in
typography for example this look at least
three letters which were  Turning in the right
place diary cute see the benefits of the
flight mode push up line and letter overshoot could
apply a base line na udaiveer optically
lyricized all the self which one you think of at
o'clock milk take that Greece they are talking
about political science in this sin but
mathematically days have different sizes
subscribe now to receive new updates
reviews and click on the subscribe button penis
size in that no before
removing his father lets
computer science of its first flight
courier destroyed with square left
side is not be criticized the right hand
side which is the state state is the size
of tropical judgment sweets clearly
evident for decades left hand side sees
maurya and square birthday to chiffon
on the right hand side optically balance and equal
scientist notification playing with this
prayer will immediately see the left hand
side will not properly scientist mixy
believe the triangle in this arvind square year
but after the optical size  Judgment inside
right hand side the triangle and square
equal last left complete the size of the
circle with triangle sided decades
left hand side sees modeler but after the
optical sizing inside come
website the circle and trying to see
mystery of equal sides are
90 by 90 and comparing sizes of
worships suggestion definition of world map to
subscribe and securely friend how much
area has been occupied by this tips
improve left hand side is difficult sizing
in right hand side is of that if you
consider the left hand side human notice
decade and square have the same with right but
the amazing is different donot balance 9 if you
consider they are overlapping on right
hand side cute see decade and here have
different button hit the find
optical area the guide to balance the
selected simple but this time and
mathematical of the
guru and square and same but once again in
the rock repairing different topics have taken
Next 9 newsroom from the right hand side is
the worst thing from the top left and
right hand click on the subscribe button similar
balance is that now let's see how this
political science in
concept applies to icons easily
subscribe icons and imaginary square
area them one square like icon will always be
slashed is engineering science
consider the following verses from the left
hand side arrived there economic border
moving forward with square [ __ ] in this
place vihar vertical board and lastly
commercial rate regions why 24 this
horizontally and vertically bird in the
forest and third place is development rate
times when i came across it comes back to keep a
similar area so as mentioned
earlier lips inscribed this icon *
imaginary square area this incident
currently for benefit miscellaneous square year but they have
already seen the non scholarships need to be up to
criticize in order to be  Persuade
equal in size the karo
your to computer to main points switch of
icons opponent special issues into this number
one company proven weight of different shade icons are
alarming visual jism and icon to
hand on the icon area number tube leaves
space between vishnu behavior icons and
icon area point number one explain how we
can optically balance non squash icons
and points number two this power has wear and
squash icons overseer technician ships
and after delivery size m.s.  Prithvi-2
points subscribe the strips in the
sense co years before you can see viewers
microns hang on the icon and square year
and always behaviour items were left some
space between them and sai kaneria co
notifications sm real icons are already
optically balanced they can usually be observed
in thriving again into square radium
but directly cancelled squares year old
doctors were is just container for mother comes
in a square is words icon and
inscribed in 200mb focusing on boys co
switch from left to right the first icon
which is square shaped is subscribe
vijendra square and no virtue all at which comes
with pencil drawing a row and clock
icon there some ticket judgments of have been made
for example the principal icon is
shooting from the top right and bottom left
corner similarly drawing and dining icon
overshoot from the top left and right side
s40 left and  right side is hanging
beyond very
next clock icon this side shooting
from all sides from force and lastly
save and its icon special hence scholarship
morning fog shooting year nav niksh women's
identity social media icons a bit already prickly
balance affair ruler will be to see
the late time judgments welcome to the twitter
instagram and improves logo ne during this time
fiercely involved in telugu all organisms to
the facebook logo hit complete square
rate for development and optical judgment
required a practical example let's look at least two
goals in terms of
mathematical science book the flying and base
line of the logo ko easy doosra dharma ke logo
very different size hai
that you can put the sizing push up line and
his line of the letters in both logos and the
same but hence withdraw element in nine lutz
push up and base line let's move
example where the copes and around
submit button diameter of the director of the crescent public
school  Bigg Boss
subscribe to the channel and subscribe to
make balance subscribe sure shooting
from the top and bottom video then
subscribe to the video then
scenes heavy penalty outline but writer no
rice water flow in today pure number one
point where you need to remember this date
of birth is how can i do subscribe button
object and necessary for its size number
to 9 scholarships need to be aware and
video clip balance subscribe kar lijiye
these stars will have some space result
from airtel balance Singh Dashrath from 10
garlic life in true spirit and learn something
from it its a good please like and
share if you have any questions or
comments please feel free to comment in the comment
section and lastly don't forget to
subscribe my channel i will see you in
next video thanks for watching